[
  {
    "cantidad1": 2,
    "cantidad2": 1,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 × 1?",
    "opciones": ["1", "2", "3"],
    "respuesta": "2"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 2,
    "cantidad2": 2,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 × 2?",
    "opciones": ["2", "4", "6"],
    "respuesta": "4"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 2,
    "cantidad2": 3,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 × 3?",
    "opciones": ["4", "6", "8"],
    "respuesta": "6"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 2,
    "cantidad2": 4,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 × 4?",
    "opciones": ["6", "8", "10"],
    "respuesta": "8"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 2,
    "cantidad2": 5,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 × 5?",
    "opciones": ["8", "10", "12"],
    "respuesta": "10"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 2,
    "cantidad2": 6,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 × 6?",
    "opciones": ["10", "12", "14"],
    "respuesta": "12"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 2,
    "cantidad2": 7,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 × 7?",
    "opciones": ["12", "14", "16"],
    "respuesta": "14"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 2,
    "cantidad2": 8,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 × 8?",
    "opciones": ["14", "16", "18"],
    "respuesta": "16"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 2,
    "cantidad2": 9,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 × 9?",
    "opciones": ["16", "18", "20"],
    "respuesta": "18"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 2,
    "cantidad2": 10,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 × 10?",
    "opciones": ["18", "20", "22"],
    "respuesta": "20"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 3,
    "cantidad2": 1,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 × 1?",
    "opciones": ["2", "3", "4"],
    "respuesta": "3"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 3,
    "cantidad2": 2,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 × 2?",
    "opciones": ["4", "6", "8"],
    "respuesta": "6"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 3,
    "cantidad2": 3,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 × 3?",
    "opciones": ["6", "9", "12"],
    "respuesta": "9"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 3,
    "cantidad2": 4,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 × 4?",
    "opciones": ["9", "12", "15"],
    "respuesta": "12"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 3,
    "cantidad2": 5,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 × 5?",
    "opciones": ["12", "15", "18"],
    "respuesta": "15"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 3,
    "cantidad2": 6,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 × 6?",
    "opciones": ["15", "18", "21"],
    "respuesta": "18"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 3,
    "cantidad2": 7,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 × 7?",
    "opciones": ["18", "21", "24"],
    "respuesta": "21"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 3,
    "cantidad2": 8,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 × 8?",
    "opciones": ["21", "24", "27"],
    "respuesta": "24"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 3,
    "cantidad2": 9,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 × 9?",
    "opciones": ["24", "27", "30"],
    "respuesta": "27"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 3,
    "cantidad2": 10,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 × 10?",
    "opciones": ["27", "30", "33"],
    "respuesta": "30"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 4,
    "cantidad2": 1,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 × 1?",
    "opciones": ["3", "4", "5"],
    "respuesta": "4"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 4,
    "cantidad2": 2,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 × 2?",
    "opciones": ["6", "8", "10"],
    "respuesta": "8"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 4,
    "cantidad2": 3,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 × 3?",
    "opciones": ["10", "12", "14"],
    "respuesta": "12"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 4,
    "cantidad2": 4,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 × 4?",
    "opciones": ["14", "16", "18"],
    "respuesta": "16"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 4,
    "cantidad2": 5,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 × 5?",
    "opciones": ["18", "20", "22"],
    "respuesta": "20"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 4,
    "cantidad2": 6,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 × 6?",
    "opciones": ["22", "24", "26"],
    "respuesta": "24"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 4,
    "cantidad2": 7,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 × 7?",
    "opciones": ["26", "28", "30"],
    "respuesta": "28"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 4,
    "cantidad2": 8,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 × 8?",
    "opciones": ["30", "32", "34"],
    "respuesta": "32"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 4,
    "cantidad2": 9,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 × 9?",
    "opciones": ["34", "36", "38"],
    "respuesta": "36"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 4,
    "cantidad2": 10,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 × 10?",
    "opciones": ["38", "40", "42"],
    "respuesta": "40"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 5,
    "cantidad2": 1,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 × 1?",
    "opciones": ["4", "5", "6"],
    "respuesta": "5"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 5,
    "cantidad2": 2,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 × 2?",
    "opciones": ["8", "10", "12"],
    "respuesta": "10"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 5,
    "cantidad2": 3,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 × 3?",
    "opciones": ["12", "15", "18"],
    "respuesta": "15"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 5,
    "cantidad2": 4,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 × 4?",
    "opciones": ["18", "20", "22"],
    "respuesta": "20"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 5,
    "cantidad2": 5,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 × 5?",
    "opciones": ["22", "25", "28"],
    "respuesta": "25"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 5,
    "cantidad2": 6,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 × 6?",
    "opciones": ["28", "30", "32"],
    "respuesta": "30"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 5,
    "cantidad2": 7,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 × 7?",
    "opciones": ["32", "35", "38"],
    "respuesta": "35"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 5,
    "cantidad2": 8,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 × 8?",
    "opciones": ["38", "40", "42"],
    "respuesta": "40"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 5,
    "cantidad2": 9,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 × 9?",
    "opciones": ["42", "45", "48"],
    "respuesta": "45"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 5,
    "cantidad2": 10,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 × 10?",
    "opciones": ["48", "50", "52"],
    "respuesta": "50"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 6,
    "cantidad2": 1,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 × 1?",
    "opciones": ["5", "6", "7"],
    "respuesta": "6"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 6,
    "cantidad2": 2,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 × 2?",
    "opciones": ["10", "12", "14"],
    "respuesta": "12"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 6,
    "cantidad2": 3,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 × 3?",
    "opciones": ["16", "18", "20"],
    "respuesta": "18"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 6,
    "cantidad2": 4,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 × 4?",
    "opciones": ["20", "24", "28"],
    "respuesta": "24"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 6,
    "cantidad2": 5,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 × 5?",
    "opciones": ["28", "30", "32"],
    "respuesta": "30"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 6,
    "cantidad2": 6,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 × 6?",
    "opciones": ["32", "36", "40"],
    "respuesta": "36"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 6,
    "cantidad2": 7,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 × 7?",
    "opciones": ["38", "42", "46"],
    "respuesta": "42"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 6,
    "cantidad2": 8,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 × 8?",
    "opciones": ["44", "48", "52"],
    "respuesta": "48"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 6,
    "cantidad2": 9,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 × 9?",
    "opciones": ["50", "54", "58"],
    "respuesta": "54"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 6,
    "cantidad2": 10,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 × 10?",
    "opciones": ["58", "60", "62"],
    "respuesta": "60"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 7,
    "cantidad2": 1,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 × 1?",
    "opciones": ["6", "7", "8"],
    "respuesta": "7"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 7,
    "cantidad2": 2,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 × 2?",
    "opciones": ["12", "14", "16"],
    "respuesta": "14"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 7,
    "cantidad2": 3,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 × 3?",
    "opciones": ["18", "21", "24"],
    "respuesta": "21"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 7,
    "cantidad2": 4,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 × 4?",
    "opciones": ["24", "28", "32"],
    "respuesta": "28"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 7,
    "cantidad2": 5,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 × 5?",
    "opciones": ["30", "35", "40"],
    "respuesta": "35"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 7,
    "cantidad2": 6,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 × 6?",
    "opciones": ["38", "42", "46"],
    "respuesta": "42"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 7,
    "cantidad2": 7,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 × 7?",
    "opciones": ["44", "49", "54"],
    "respuesta": "49"
  }
  ,
  {
    "cantidad1": 7,
    "cantidad2": 8,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 × 8?",
    "opciones": ["54", "56", "60"],
    "respuesta": "56"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 7,
    "cantidad2": 9,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 × 9?",
    "opciones": ["60", "63", "66"],
    "respuesta": "63"
  },
  {
    "cantidad1": 7,
    "cantidad2": 10,
    "operacion": "×",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 × 10?",
    "opciones": ["66", "70", "74"],
    "respuesta": "70"
  } 
]